So, the recording has started.  Great, friends.
Hi all.  Welcome to the
Setka Project channel.  And today we'll
talk about these cool things
called
neural network comparison aggregators.  What is this?  Uh,
imagine, you want to see
how you can disperse it somehow, it doesn’t matter,
there, and this is this new Imagine
4.0 or this nano banana, which is Gni 2 with
12. Here.  And you want, let's say, to compare
them, yes, that is, Imagines Nanoban,
to see which generates
photos better, how it processes prompts,
or, let's say, compare other
neural networks.   It
doesn't matter whether these are neural networks for creating
photographs or neural networks that
work with text prompts.  What do
you need to do for this?  You need to
register on one site,
complete a couple of generations there, and then you will need to register on another site
, and
complete a couple of generations there.  But there are sites
called
neural network comparison aggregators.  They provide access to
absolutely all neural networks.  And you can
compare one
with the other in real time.  And there are such sites.  This site,
well, let's analyze two sites.   The
first site is LM arena.
Where is she?  Here it is, the LM arena.  And the second
site is called.
These are our, uh,
neural network comparison aggregators.  Let's quickly
register with them.
How to work with UP?  Let me explain.  Look, a
window for entering prompts opens.
Actually, we are introducing promt.  We
choose that it will be a photograph.  That
is, we will
generate a photograph based on this prompt.  Oh, and we can
choose any model we're interested in
for comparison, or
choose nothing, it will choose everything itself.
Let's start without choosing a model.
So, I have a prompt in
English.  You can, of course, try to
display the prompt in Russian, but
some neural networks won't be very
good at understanding what's expected of them in
Russian.  Universal English will
do just fine.  So,
my promt is a super-realistic
photograph.
So, there is a
donkey standing in the desert.  The cat sits on a donkey
and
plays the guitar.  And there is a
rooster sitting on the cat's head.  Well, let's try.
Fine.  And for this project we had
two generations.  The first generation from
Google Imagine,
the second from Flux.
And I think the first generation was
once bigger, but the meaning is not conveyed.  So
I need a donkey with a
cat playing the guitar on it, and a rooster sitting on the cat's head
.
Here.  And we spent, I think
, about 100 credits on this generation.  Now
we need to evaluate which photograph is
better.  I think the left photo is better.
Why?  Because, well, let's say she's
faster, uh, she, I
don't know, that's how I evaluate it.
And she is better, she is more stylish.  She is also more
interesting.
And the second photo of the flux, it’s somehow
wrong, it’s slow.
We give our assessment, and this is the
card that appears.
We erase this card and we receive
credits for our vote.  That is, we spent,
roughly speaking, 100 credits and received
583.
Let's enter this prompt again.
I don't see the cat.   This is
somehow more interesting to me.
Earn credits.  It doesn't matter what you
click here.
616 credits.  Great.  Let's
enter this prompt again.
For this promt
they take 100 credits from us.
Now we will have Cdream and again the
content Pro hatch.
This is what we wanted.  SDIM 4.0.   A
donkey, a
cat with a guitar and a rooster on the cat's head.
We vote for him, of course,
and receive 174 credits.  And we now have
5.46
credits.  I liked this version of CDAM 4.0
.  What do we do now?
Let's re-enter our prompt and
select the Cdream model.   This
model we had was Cdream 4.0
Max.   Let's
compare it with something else.
M. GBT idzh is good.
This is how complete the photo turned out to be.
I vote for GPT id.
And we were given 300 credits for this.  Great.
If you need a specific model,
select that specific model here.
Let's choose,
enter our prompt, choose a photo,
let's choose, well, let's say, let's choose this
new nanoban.
Nanobana.
Let's see how this industrial
turns out in nanobans.
Here we have a nano banana and compared it with
GPT Image 1.
Well, not bad, not bad.
There are photographs, they were taken practically for
free.  Let's vote and get
our loans.
[music]
To reliably receive credits,
you need to enter the prom without choosing any
neural network for generation.
Then you will receive 100% credits for your vote
.
If you try, you will never run out of loans
I like it better,
300 credits.
Great.  We chose the first photo.  And
we can work with this photograph right here
.  That is, I want
to change something in this photo.  Let's, let's,
uh, let the donkey have glasses.
Glasses on a donkey and a cat
electric guitar.
Please.
You can create a new chat and work with
new photos.
And if we don’t select a photo,
then we will compare models for
text prompts.  For example,
write a
poem about a donkey and a cat.
He gives the first verse.  Ihom courtyard in the
evening light.  A heavy donkey walks along the
path.  In the courtyard along the path.
Eh, player three gives us the answer.  A donkey walked
along a dusty path, pulling a cart and puffing
sadly.  Suddenly a
playful cat with its tail came towards us.   The
fluffy child
quietly hums the ice of summer, warming the soul.  Ah, well,
I liked the third player better.
Well, especially since the stick
turned out so long.  It's a real poem.  And we vote for the
player
and get 411 credits.  Great.  Do
you understand the gist of how to use UP?
There is also this thing in Yupa: leaders.
You can see who people vote for the
most.  That is, in this case we
select engine.
So, Cream is in first place for us.  Next
comes Gini.  GPT first.
Well, and text ones.
Opus 4, GPT 5.
That is, well, take a look, choose for
yourself what interests you most, both
text and for creating
photographs.
And this is quite live communication
.  Let's move on to MREA.
Here, in principle, everything is the same.
We select a photo and enter our prompt.
Let's launch.  Yes, I agree.
But here we are not shown
which network generated which photo
.  We will have, for example,
network A and network B. After we
vote, then this
terrible secret will be revealed.  Who generated what photos for us?
I like this one better
because I ordered the rooster to
sit.  Ah, although there is a rooster
sitting on my shoulders here.  Well, anyway, I’m going to, uh,
vote for this
and you’re revealing a terrible secret to me.
Yes, I am human.
And this is our Gimini.  This is an idiogram.
How does it all work?
We have three options, so to speak, for
launching the arena.  The first is a battle.  That
is, you enter a prompt, and you don’t know
which neural network will generate your prompt.
Two photos will be generated.  So
you choose the best one you
like the most, and then LM Arena
tells you
which neural network is responsible for which
photo.  Here.  And here you can also
compare two neural networks, that is, indicate
them.  Let's try.  Okay, let's make a new
chat.
This is what we're going to have, uh,
Imagine 4.0, my favorite.  And let's make it a
nano banana.  Imagine
4.0.
Oh, Ultra.  Imagine 4.0.  Ultra.  Here she is.
This is my favorite.  And nanobana.
Here she is, just like that.  Gini 2.5 nanoban.
We enter our promt.  Let's go.
So, Nanona Banana
generated faster.
Imagin Ultra is slower, but the code here is
somehow more lively.
Look, there's some kind of dust coming out.  Let's
increase it.  He was apparently quickly moving towards his goal
of showing us a cat with a
rooster sitting on its head.
And here the cat
turned out to be some kind of cartoon.
Ah, well, let's choose the left one.
You won't get any credits for voting here
.  That is the
only thing that confirmation
constantly gets on my nerves.
Thank you.
Now let's
try some more serious prompts
in the new chat.  I prepared a prompt in advance
, according to which I will make a video.  And
let's score this promt
in Yupi.
Let's choose the models right away.  This will be the
Let's Banana model.
Nanobana promt is
quite long.
Let's launch.
I'm currently creating photos for this project
and
will be making a new video clip from the photos using Grok.  I'll definitely
post it.
Okay, let's see.
Some kind of 3D model
in nanobana.  A GPT image is one mini.
So, well, I liked GPT better,
of course.  I vote.
Everything is okay.
And we got it for it.  We didn't get anything for it
, because we chose the model
ourselves.
So, let's do the same thing in the arena now
.
We select Image.
We will choose the model.  And here is my
favorite Imagen 4 Ultra.
And here we will choose.  Come on, let there be the
same ban.
So, they introduced promt.
Let's see what
comes out of this.
Nana Banana took, in principle, a very
interesting photo.
And Imagine 4 Ultra is more lively and
realistic.
And I choose this
left one, 4.0 ultra.
Now, he'll probably come again.
Oh no, it came.  I thought there would be no
confirmation that I am a human being and that I am
indeed voting as a human being.
Yes, I confirm.
See what this is for.
Imagine you choose some
neural network to generate your
photos because, well, let's
be honest, different neural networks
perceive prompts differently and
sometimes generate such gibberish from a pretty good
prompt that these prompts
need to be processed somewhere.  So,
imagine you took some kind of
neural network, for example,
well, I don’t know, there’s the same Image 4.0
Ultra, and in order not to waste
your paid credits, you need to, let’s say,
prepare some prompts so that
everything looks nice in the
photo, and so that the necessary things
are placed in the right places.  Oh, and
this prompt can be worked out very well in the same LM arena on
Imagine 4.0 Ultra
, that is, to see how
everything will look there.  Here.  And when your
prompt is ready, please
generate it in the paid versions.
Imagine 4.0.  I just gave an example.  It
could be an insane number of
neural networks.  So what kind of neural networks are there
here?
Well, in principle, there is quite a large selection here
,
but in YUP, which is why I included YUB
in the review, YUP has many more of these neural networks
.
Selecting a model.
Selecting a model for
photographs.
And here are our models
that we can try.  I mean,
well, look, an insane amount.
And we can run each one, that is,
we can run our
industrial model through each one, and see which neural network is
more suitable for creating a photograph, and
which is less suitable.
Here.  In general, these are
interesting sites,
use them,
and create your own prompts, bring them to
perfection.
Ah, download it and put it into the game,
make a video, and we'll see what happens.
Well, to sum up everything that has been said above, what do
these sites actually give us? They
give us the real opportunity
to use various neural networks for free to
generate images and for some
text queries.  And they give us the
opportunity
to compare different photo generation models
.  Here.  and, uh, based on the
comparison results, choose the best
model.  As for me,
they really help me a lot in
processing the prompts, that is, in bringing
these prompts to perfection.  I can actually
play around with some kind of generation model for free
.  I can create a promt, uh,
test it on this model and when it's
ready, I can implement it in the paid
version of this model.  This is great.
And when new generation models come out,
when they are added to these sites, I can
study them, see how they
work, compare them with the models
I am currently working with.  In general, the
tool, well, at least for me, is
very useful.
Well, and here's a very important point.  You must
understand that this is a demonstration, and that
you will not see the highest quality images here
.  And basically they make
square images with the size of 1024 by
1024 pixels.  Some generation models
produce vertical
images like these 1024 x 1536.
Ah, but they are still far from ideal,
but at least it’s free.  And this is a huge
number of neural networks for free.  And maybe this
will be enough for someone.
So, make some promts, polish them
, make some
video clips,
send them to our Telegram group, we'll
take a look, evaluate them, and offer advice.  In
general, use it.  I hope this
will be as useful to someone as it was to me.  Oh, and don't
forget about the copyright for
creating images.  This is really very
important.  Well, that's all from me.
Subscribe to never
miss a thing.  Until next time.